我不想打断你们  但是...
I hate to interrupt you, but the reason we're here...
有样东西我希望你能看一下
Yes. I have something to show you.
我留你父亲自己在图书馆工作
I left your father working in the library.
当时他请我去拿旧都市计划图
He sent me to the map section to fetch an ancient plan of the city.
我回来时发现他跟文件不见了
When I got back to his table, he'd gone, with all his papers,
只剩下这张纸  在他的椅子旁边发现的
except for that scrap, which I found near his chair.
是罗马数字
Roman numerals.
图书馆到了
Here is the library.
它看起来一点都不像图书馆
That doesn't look much like a library.
比较像是教堂
Looks like a converted church.
一点都没错
In this case, it's the literal truth.
你们来到了圣地
We are on holy ground.
这些柱子饱受战火蹂躏  之后被送来这里
These columns over here were brought back as spoils of war